H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 4: Senatorial Career, 1931-1958; 159.67 linear feet 376 boxes
  - Subseries 4F: Senate Committees, 1945-1958; 51.08 linear feet 123 boxes
    - Education and Labor Committee/Labor and Public Welfare Committee, 1945-1958; 41 boxes (2 partial)
      - 1950-1951, 2 boxes
        - Agricultural Workers from Mexico, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Army, Morale, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Basing Point, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Defense Production Act, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Emergency Seizure Legislation, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Fair Employment Practices Act, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Federal Highway Bill, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Financial Assistance for Local Education, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Ford Foundation, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Health Legislation, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Housing, Comments and Clippings, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Internal Security Act, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Labor-Management Relations Act, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Natural Gas Act, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - National Science Foundation, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Oleo Bill, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Postal Rates, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Railway Labor Act, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Renegotiation Act, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Rent Control, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Republican Advance, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Social Security, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Subcommittee on Health, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Taft-Hartley Act, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Tax Bill, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Trenton Six, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Unemployment Compensation, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Veterans’ Affairs, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Wisconsin Anti-Strike Law, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - 1952-1953, 5 boxes
        - Accident Prevention, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Appropriations, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1952-1953; 3 folders
          - General, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Holderman, Carl, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Consumers’ Price Index, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Federal Reorganization Plans, President Hoover, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Health Information Foundation, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Health Legislation, Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Hospital Construction ,1953, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - International Labor Organization, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Korean Veterans G. I. Bill, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Labor Disputes, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Labor Settlements, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Migratory Labor, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - National Science Foundation, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - National Science Foundation, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - National Science Foundation, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Steel Seizure Case, 1952; 2 folders (Folder 2 to 3)
        - Subcommittee on Health, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Taft-Hartley, 1953; portions of 2 boxes
          - Amendments, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 5)
          - Amendments, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Letter to the President, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Unemployment Compensation, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Unions and Communism, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Wage and Price Controls, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous, 1953; 3 folders (Folder 4 to 6)
      - 1954, 6 boxes (1 partial)
        - General, 1954; 2 folders (Folder 1 to 2)
        - Administration’s Legislative Program, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Agriculture, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Appropriations Bill, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Beeson, Albert Cummins, Nomination, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Bills, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Congress of Industrial Organizations, Unemployment Insurance, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Congressional and Judicial Salaries, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Education Bills, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Health Reinsurance Bill, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Health, Speeches and Releases, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Labor-Management Bills, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Labor Youth League, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - McCarthy, Senator Joseph, 1954; 2 folders (Folder 2 to 3)
        - National Science Foundation, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Railroad Retirement Act, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Rodgers, Philip Ray, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Rules for Committee, Investigations, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Strikes, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Taft-Hartley, 1954; portions of 2 boxes
          - General, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - Correspondence, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
          - Debate, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 6)
          - Hearings, Testimony, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - National Association of Manufacturers, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Statements, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Unemployment Compensation Program, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - United States Attorney for New Jersey, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Veterans’ Affairs, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Wage Stabilization, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1954; 2 folders (Folder 5 to 6)
      - 1955-1957, 12 boxes (2 partial)
        - General, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - General, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Agricultural Act, Repeal, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - AFL-CIO, General, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - AFL-CIO, Merger, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Area Assistance Act, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Bible Reading in Schools, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Brown, Newell, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Chemical Additives, Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Colorado River Storage Project, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Defense Department, Appropriations, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Dental and Medical Research and Training Act, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Disabled Veterans, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Education, General, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Education, General, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Education Beyond the High School, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Education, White House Conference, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Educational Loan Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Eight-Hour Laws, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Equal Pay Bill, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1957; 2 folders (Folder 5 to 6)
        - Federal Aid to States, Safety Laws, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Federal Advisory Commission on the Arts, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Federal Advisory Council of Health, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Federal Employees’ Compensation Act, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Federal Equal Pay Act, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Federal Medical Services, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Gasoline Price War in New Jersey, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - General Extension Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Health, Education, and Welfare Committee, Creation of, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Health Insurance, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Health Research Facilities Act, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Housing, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Hoover Commission, 1955; portions of 2 boxes
          - Bills, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 12)
          - Bills, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Comparative Print, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Federal Medical Services, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - McCarthy, Senator Joseph, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Improper Activities in the Labor or Management Field, Select Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Independent Unions, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Industrial Safety Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - International Labor Organization, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Labor, General, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Labor, General, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Labor, General, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Library Services Act, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Longshoremen and Harbor Workers’ Compensation Act, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Mental Health, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Mental Health Bill, Alaska, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Mentally Handicapped Children, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Migratory Labor, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Minimum Wage, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Minimum Wage, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - National Institute of Dental Research, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - National Labor Relations Board, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - National Library of Medicine, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - National Science Foundation, Speech, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - National Science Foundation, Miscellaneous, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Nursing Services Commission, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Polio, 1955-1956; 4 folders
          - Hearing, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Vaccine, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Postal Service, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Production of Statements and Reports of Witnesses, Supreme Court Decision, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Public Health Service Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Saint Elizabeth’s Hospital, Salaries, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Salary Increase, Congress and Judiciary, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - School Construction, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - School Construction, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - School Construction, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - School Construction, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Scientific Research, Joint Committee, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Scientists and Engineers, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Senate Rules, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Small Business Tax Reduction, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Taft-Hartley, 1956-1957; 5 folders
          - General, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Building and Construction Industry, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Hospitals, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - National Labor Relations Board, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
          - Union Reports, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Unions, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Veterans, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Veterans’ Reorganization Act, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Vocational Education, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Welfare and Benefit Plans Registration Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Welfare and Pension Funds, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Work Hours Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Work Hours Law, District of Columbia, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Workmen’s Compensation, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - 1958, 6 boxes (2 partial)
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Area Economic Redevelopment Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Coal Mine Safety Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Education, 1958; portions of 2 boxes
          - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
          - Assistance, Federally Affected Areas, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
          - Cooperative Research, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
          - Educational Development Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
          - Educational Financial Assistance Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
          - Educational Loan Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
          - Exclusion of Business and Commercial Schools from Administration Education Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
          - Flanders Education Bills, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
          - Foreign Languages, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - National Defense Education Act, 1958; 2 folders (Folder 2 to 3)
          - National Student Association, Press Conference, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
          - Rockefeller Report, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
          - Scholarships, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
          - Tax Deductions for Teachers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Federal Advisory Commission on the Arts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Freedman’s Hospital, Howard University, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Hospital Construction, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Juvenile Delinquency Bills, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Kohler Strike, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Labor, General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Labor-Management Legislation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1958; 3 folders
          - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Amendments, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Statement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Labor Reports Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Labor Union Registration Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Longshoremen and Harbor Workers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Medal for Distinguished Civilian Achievement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Medical and Dental Research and Training, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - National Labor Relations Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - National Labor Relations Board, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - National Science Foundation, 1958; portions of 2 boxes
          - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
          - Appropriations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
          - Scholarships, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Scientists and Engineers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Older Persons, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Public Health Service Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Railroad Retirement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Railroads, Transportation Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Rehabilitation Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - School Assistance Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - School Construction Assistance Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Science, General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Science and Technology Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Scientist and Technician Manpower Shortage, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Small Business, 1958; 4 folders
          - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
          - Military Contracts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
          - Small Business Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
          - Tax Problems, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Social Security, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Space Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Supreme Court, Appellate Jurisdiction Limitations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Supreme Court, Federal Pre-Emption, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Taxes, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Telecasts, Fees for Home Viewing, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Textile Industry, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Unemployment, 1958; 3 folders
          - Capehart Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
          - Compensation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
          - Employment, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Veterans’ Affairs, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Veterans’ Children Scholarship Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - War Hazards Compensation Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Water Resources, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Welfare and Pension Fund Act, 1958; 2 folders (Folder 1 to 2)
        - Wilderness Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Zinc Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1958; 2 folders (Folder 5 to 6)
    - Other Committees, 1945-1946; 2 boxes (1 partial)
      - District of Columbia Committee, Zoning, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Judiciary Committee, 1945-1946; portions of 2 boxes
        - Equal Rights Amendment, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Federal Reorganization Bill, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Foreign Contracts, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Insurance, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Reorganization Procedure Bill, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Subcommittee, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1945; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Military Affairs Committee, Miscellaneous, 1946; 2 folders (Folder 7 to 8)
      - Privileges and Elections Committee, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Other Committees, undated; 1 item
  - Subseries 4G: Speeches, Addresses, and Engagements, 1931-1958; 6.05 linear feet 15 boxes
    The Speeches and Addresses subseries includes documents related to public appearances and publications. The Articles and Speeches section contains both drafts and printed articles and speeches. The bulk of the documents were either penned by Smith or relate directly to him. Some of this material pre-dates his Senate tenure. The Itineraries section contains daily logs of Smith’s activities. They also note meetings and appointments. The itineraries cover Smith’s Senate activities. The Engagements section consists of correspondence, programs and other documents related to Smith’s public appearances and meetings. The Appointment Books section consists of date books in which Smith listed appointments such as lunches and meetings. The Statements section includes press releases and statements to the media from Smith.
    The Speeches and Addresses Subseries is arranged in five sections: Articles and Speeches, Itineraries, Engagements, Appointment Books, and Statements. Smith's original order has been maintained.
    - Articles and Speeches, 1931-1958; 4 boxes
      - Arthur Krok, Presidential Election, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Educational Statement, Institute of International Education News Bulletin, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Columbian Civil League, Columbus Day, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Commercial and Financial Chronicle, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Community Conference Program and White House Conference on Education, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service, Freedom, Independence and Self Determination, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Bond Club Speech, New York, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Foreign Policy Town Meeting, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Bipartisanship and Foreign Policy, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Europa Magazine, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Economic Outlook and the Foreign Front, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Philadelphia Chronicle Statement, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - World Affairs, Situations in the Far East, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Constantine Brown Column Article, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - New Approach to Labor Law, Interview, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Panel Discussion, Ideological War with Communism, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Labor Department Speech, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Foreign Policy Bulletin, Peiping, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Columbia Law School News Article, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Cumberland County Medical Society Dinner, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Calvary Church Speech, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Wilson College, 80th Anniversary, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - America’s Health, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Republican Magazine, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Oberlin Speech, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Freedom For a Dynamic America, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - S. O. S. From the Colleges, 1931; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Lincoln Day Address, Trenton, 1944; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Speeches and Broadcasts, 1944-1948; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Radio, Blair Moody, Fiscal Matters, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Radio and Television Broadcast Transcripts, 1944-1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Waging the War of Words Talks, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Robert College, Stamboul, Turkey, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Edison Birthplace Association, 1953-1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Articles by Smith, 1952-1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Prospects for Peace, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - One Great Hour of Sharing, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Prospects for Peace, World Affairs, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - American Heritage of Freedom, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Freedom Shrine Dedication, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Newark Academy Commencement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Woodrow Wilson School, Collective Security, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Prospects for Peace, Farm Bureau, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Republican Dinner, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Commercial and Financial Chronicle, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Compulsory Health Insurance, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - United States Relations with India, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Atlantic City, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Labor Unions, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - United States Foreign Aid Policy Pros and Cons, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Minimum Wage, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - National Science Foundation Speech, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - League of Women Voters, Eisenhower Doctrine, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Modern Republicanism, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Atlantic City Bar Association, Foreign Policy, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Woodrow Wilson, Centennial Celebration, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Ukrainian Speech Rally, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Camden Chamber of Commerce Speech, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Speech Material, 1934-1937; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Foreign Policy Speech Material, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Foreign Policy, Miscellaneous, 1950-1956; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - United Nations, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous Drafts, 1942-1956; 5 folders
        - 1942-1945, 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - 1946, 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - 1947-1948, 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - 1949-1950, 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - 1952-1956, 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Itineraries, 1951-1958; 2 boxes (1 partial)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - 1953-1955, 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - 1955-1957, 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - 1958, 1 folder (Folder 2)